<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<module><name>script_fb_channel</name><description>Improvements of the JS SDK.&#13;
Adding a Channel File greatly improves the performance of the JS SDK by addressing issues with cross-domain communication in certain browsers.&#13;
&#13;
The channel file should be set to be cached for as long as possible. When serving this file, you should send valid Expires headers with a long expiration period. This will ensure the channel file is cached by the browser and not reloaded with each page refresh. Without proper caching, users will suffer a severely degraded experience.&#13;
&#13;
The channelUrl parameter within FB.init() is optional, but strongly recommended. Providing a channel file can help address three specific known issues.&#13;
&#13;
- Pages that include code to communicate across frames may cause Social Plugins to show up as blank without a channelUrl.&#13;
- if no channelUrl is provided and a page includes auto-playing audio or video, the user may hear two streams of audio because the page has been loaded a second time in the background for cross domain communication.&#13;
- a channel file will prevent inclusion of extra hits in your server-side logs. If you do not specify a channelUrl, you should remove page views containing fb_xd_bust or fb_xd_fragment parameters from your logs to ensure proper counts.&#13;
&#13;
The channelUrl must be a fully qualified URL matching the page on which you include the SDK. In other words, the channel file domain must include www if your site is served using www, and if you modify document.domain on your page you must make the same document.domain change in the channel.html file as well. The protocols must also match. If your page is served over https, your channelUrl must also be https. Remember to use the matching protocol for the script src as well. The sample code above uses protocol-relative URLs which should handle most https cases properly.</description><type/><alias>script_fb_channel</alias></module>
